final List<Map<String, dynamic>> LecOneQuiz = [
  {
    'question': 'What is cerebral palsy?',
    'options': [
      'A genetic disorder',
      'A neurological disorder',
      'A respiratory disorder',
      'A cardiovascular disorder'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'A neurological disorder',
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which part of the body does cerebral palsy primarily affect?',
    'options': ['Heart', 'Lungs', 'Muscles and motor skills', 'Kidneys'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Muscles and motor skills',
  },
  {
    'question': 'Is cerebral palsy a progressive condition?',
    'options': ['True', 'False'],
    'correctAnswer': 'False',
  },
  {
    'question': 'What are common symptoms of cerebral palsy?',
    'options': [
      'Shortness of breath',
      'Motor skill impairments',
      'High blood pressure',
      'Frequent infections'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'Motor skill impairments',
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of the following is a risk factor for cerebral palsy?',
    'options': [
      'Premature birth',
      'Smoking',
      'High cholesterol',
      'High altitude'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'Premature birth',
  },
  {
    'question': 'What type of disorder is cerebral palsy?',
    'options': ['Degenerative', 'Non-degenerative', 'Genetic', 'Infectious'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Non-degenerative',
  },
  {
    'question': 'Which of the following is NOT a type of cerebral palsy?',
    'options': ['Spastic', 'Dyskinetic', 'Ataxic', 'Neuropathic'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Neuropathic',
  },
  {
    'question': 'Can cerebral palsy affect cognitive function?',
    'options': ['Yes', 'No'],
    'correctAnswer': 'Yes',
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which of the following therapies is commonly used for cerebral palsy?',
    'options': [
      'Chemotherapy',
      'Physical therapy',
      'Radiation therapy',
      'Dialysis'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'Physical therapy',
  },
  {
    'question': 'What causes cerebral palsy?',
    'options': [
      'Brain damage before, during, or shortly after birth',
      'Infection in early childhood',
      'Autoimmune response',
      'Genetic mutation'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'Brain damage before, during, or shortly after birth',
  },
];

final List<Map<String, dynamic>> LecTwoQuiz = [
  {
    'question': 'Which test is commonly used to diagnose cerebral palsy?',
    'options': ['Blood test', 'MRI scan', 'X-ray', 'ECG'],
    'correctAnswer': 'MRI scan',
  },
  {
    'question': 'At what age is cerebral palsy typically diagnosed?',
    'options': [
      'During pregnancy',
      'At birth',
      'In early childhood',
      'In adulthood'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'In early childhood',
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which specialist is typically involved in diagnosing cerebral palsy?',
    'options': [
      'Cardiologist',
      'Neurologist',
      'Pulmonologist',
      'Dermatologist'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'Neurologist',
  },
  {
    'question': 'Is genetic testing required to diagnose cerebral palsy?',
    'options': ['True', 'False'],
    'correctAnswer': 'False',
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which physical sign might suggest cerebral palsy in an infant?',
    'options': [
      'Rapid weight gain',
      'Muscle stiffness',
      'Frequent colds',
      'Bright red skin'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'Muscle stiffness',
  },
  {
    'question': 'Can cerebral palsy be detected with a prenatal ultrasound?',
    'options': ['Yes', 'No'],
    'correctAnswer': 'No',
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which type of imaging is useful for assessing brain abnormalities in cerebral palsy?',
    'options': ['Ultrasound', 'CT scan', 'PET scan', 'Mammogram'],
    'correctAnswer': 'CT scan',
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is a common sign of cerebral palsy in young children?',
    'options': [
      'Delayed milestones',
      'High fever',
      'Persistent cough',
      'Skin rash'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'Delayed milestones',
  },
  {
    'question':
        'Which prenatal factor can increase the risk of cerebral palsy?',
    'options': [
      'Maternal infections',
      'High maternal age',
      'Excessive exercise',
      'Low maternal weight'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'Maternal infections',
  },
  {
    'question': 'What is the primary method for diagnosing cerebral palsy?',
    'options': [
      'Observing developmental progress and motor skills',
      'Blood tests',
      'Urine tests',
      'Hearing tests'
    ],
    'correctAnswer': 'Observing developmental progress and motor skills',
  },
];
